Guide to the Stanford University, School of Engineering, Dean's Office, Records SC0165
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Annual Reports to the President, Series 4
  - Reports, 1950-1956 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Electrical Engineering, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Dean's Office, 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Mechanical Engineering, 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Dean's Office, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Dean's Office, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Civil Engineering, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Dean's Office, 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Mechanical Engineering, 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Aero and Astro, 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Dean's Office, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Civil Engineering, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Industrial Engineering, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Reports, 1956-1958 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Dean's Office, 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Industrial Engineering, 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Mechanical Engineering, 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Dean's Office, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Civil Engineering, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Electrical Engineering, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Industrial Engineering, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Mechanical Engineering, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Reports, 1958-1960 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Dean's Office, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Aeronautical Engineering, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Civil Engineering, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Electrical Engineering, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Industrial Engineering, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Mechanical Engineering, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Dean's Office, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Aeronautical Engineering, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Chemical Engineering, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Civil Engineering, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Mechanical Engineering, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Metallurgical Engineering, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Staff paper on changes involving Departments of Chemical Engineering and Metallurgical Engineering, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Reports, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Dean's Office, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Aeronautical Engineering, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Chemical Engineering, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Civil Engineering, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Electrical Engineering, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Industrial Engineering, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Materials Science, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Mechanical Engineering, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Reports, 1962-1964 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Dean's Office, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Dean's Office, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Aero and Astro, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Chemical Engineering, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Civil Engineering, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Electrical Engineering, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Industrial Engineering, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Materials Sciences, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Mechanical Engineering, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Minutes, Series 5
  - School of Engineering, Executive Committee, 1925-1927 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - School of Engineering, Executive Committee, 1931-1944 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - School of Engineering, Exec Committee Minutes, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - School of Engineering, Exec Committee Minutes, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - School of Engineering, Exec Committee Minutes, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - School of Engineering, Exec Committee Minutes, 1950-1952 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - School of Engineering, Exec Committee Minutes, 1953-1957 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - School of Engineering, Faculty Meetings, 1925-1927 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - School of Engineering, Faculty Meetings, 1931-1947 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - School of Engineering, Faculty Meetings, 1948-1954 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Civil Engineering, Faculty Minutes, 1923-1939 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Civil Engineering, Faculty Minutes, 1930-1939 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Civil Engineering, Faculty Minutes, 1940-1951 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Civil Engineering, Faculty Minutes, 1952-1958 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Electrical Engineering, Faculty Minutes, 1917-1918 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Electrical Engineering, Faculty Minutes, 1919-1920 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Electrical Engineering, Faculty Minutes, 1921-1924 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Electrical Engineering, Faculty Minutes, 1925-1946 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Electrical Engineering, Executive Committee, 1962-1964 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Electrical Engineering, Graduate Administration Committee, 1962-1964 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Electrical Engineering, Undergraduate Administration Committee, 1962-1964 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Mechanical Engineering, Department Meetings, 1918-1928 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Mechanical Engineering, Department Meetings, 1929-1941 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Additional records, Accession ARCH-1990-150
  - Correspondence (Dean's) and miscellaneous notes re buildings, 1928-1942 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Mechanical Engineering, reports on equipment and buildings, 1936, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - J.B. Wells, notes re construction of engineering buildings, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Architectural drawings (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Additional records, Accession ARCH-1994-147
  - Applications to graduate division (Stanford grads), 1947-1957 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Faculty meetings, minutes, 1925 Oct-1933 Oct (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Faculty meetings, minutes, 1934 Jan-1941 Aug (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Faculty meetings, minutes, 1942 Jan-1945 May (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Faculty meetings, minutes, 1946 Jan-1950 Apr (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Scheduling Committee, minutes, 1925-1926 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Registration and graduation committee, minutes [bound volume], 1925-1957 (Box 1)
- Additional records, Accession ARCH-2010-088
- Additional records, Accession ARCH-2018-070